======================= Fix or feedback: please let me know truc1979@laposte.net =======================
======================= Fix or feedback: please let me know truc1979@laposte.net =======================
Taxi!
Taxi !
So say! Make the queue like everyone else!
Dîtes donc! Faîtes la queue comme tout le monde!
"The queue, I fuck her"
"La queue, I fuck her"
- She's so rude! - You know what that mean that? - It means that she does not care about my queue
- Elle est grossière en plus! - Tu sais ce que ca veut dire ca? - Ca veut dire qu'elle se fout de ma queue
To the "4 soeurs" please
To the "4 soeurs" please
Have you seen? Just landed in France and already believes in conquered territory
Non mais vous vous rendez compte? A peine débarquée en France et ca se croit déjà en terrain conquis
It's an American, you can see it right away
C'est une américaine, ca se voit tout de suite
Do you think she would apologize ?!
Vous croyez qu'elle s'excuserait?!
Oh, slow down
Oh, slow down
Cowboy, huh?
Cowboy, huh?
She wants a cowboy she will have one...
Elle veut du cowboy elle va en avoir...
Slow down, you gonna kill me
Slow down, you gonna kill me
- Please slow down - "Slow down, slow down" you'll see I'm a man
- Please slow down - "slow down, slow down", you'll see I'm a man
It will worth your money, beauty
Tu vas en avoir pour ton argent ma belle
Okay, see what you've got ...
Ok, see what you've got...
Where it goes like that? Hey, slowly, it is fragile my thing.
Où elle va comme ca? Hey, doucement, c'est fragile mon truc.
Hard already?
Hard already?
She wastes no time
Elle ne perd pas de temps celle-là.
Hey be careful: we're on the road there.
Hey attention on est sur la route là.
I show you what american girl can do
I show you what american girl can do
"branler" (means: handjob)
"Branler" (means: handjob)
Oh for God.
Ah nom de Dieu.
Good "branler", "good"
Good "branler", "bien"
"Dis, dis" (Means: Say, say)
"Dis, dis!" (means: tell, tell)
"Dis", she's funny, but it is not easy.
"Dis", elle est marrante, mais avec ce qu'elle fait ce n'est pas facile.
Nice french
Nice french
Yes, I understand, here we are in Paris. There are friends of yours in the "4 soeurs" street?
Oui, j'ai compris, on est à Paris ici. C'est des copains à vous rue des 4 soeurs?
Yeah, my friends are very nice too.
Yeah, my friends are very nice too.
My name is Jeannot. thirty
Moi c'est Jeannot.
You like that Jeannot?
You like that Jeannot?
If you take me through feelings is not bad but ...
Si tu me prends par les sentiments c'est pas mal mais...
with my job it's not very advisable
dans mon métier ce n'est pas trop conseillé.
Ooh bitch ...
Ouh la salope...
LA BAISE AMERICAINE (American Fuck)
LA BAISE AMERICAINE (American Fuck)
I love Paris it's a beautiful town
I love Paris it's a beautiful town
Here is the "route de l'Etoile"
Ici c'est la route de l'étoile.
I love Paris
I love Paris
Yes, you love my fly
Ma braguette oui
I like sight-seeing
I like sight-seeing
So do I! I like the "sinksing-in-paris!"
Et moi donc! J'aime le "sinksing-in-paris"!
Nice
Nice
- I know that's Sacre Coeur
- I know that's Sacré-Coeur
- Already? I didn't notice the time
- Déjà? Je n'ai pas vu le temps passer
If my wife saw me ...
Si ma femme me voyait...
Hey, won't you stop? You give me seasick!
Non mais ce n'est pas bientôt fini! Vous me donnez le mal de mer!
Oh, I'll swing my yogurt in the throat. Hurry up...
Ah je vais balancer mon yaourt dans la gorge. Dépêche-toi...
You bastard! You can't watch where you're going?
Espèce d'enfoiré! Vous ne pouvez pas regarder où vous allez?
Not really. It can happen to anyone
Pas tellement. Ca peut arriver à tout le monde
And he's a taxi driver!
Et c'est chauffeur de taxi!
What are you doing?
Qu'est-ce que vous foutez?
- Well, okay, watch out next time ... - What are you waiting for?
- Bon, d'accord, mais la prochaine fois... - Alors, on prend racine?
Can't you see you're in a prohibited direction? Be gently.
Non mais vous ne voyez pas que vous êtes dans un sens interdit? Alors doucement.
Never mind, there is no hurry.
Ca ne fait rien, on n'est pas pressés.
Thank you
Thank you
Okay well that's 200 Francs
Bon ben ça fait 200 Francs
- 200 Francs - Yes, the ride, it's 200 francs for me.
- 200 Francs - Oui, le trajet, ça fait 200 Francs pour moi.
200 Francs.
200 Francs.
yes
yes
If my wife knew that ...
Si ma femme savait ça...
(200 Francs for a blowjob)
(200 Francs la pipe)
Thank you
Merci beaucoup
The pleasure is mine
Tout le plaisir est pour moi
Good bye, young lady
Au revoir mademoiselle
John Prick please? He's not home?
John Prick please? He's not home?
He's not home. Just wait here. Come in
Il n'est pas chez lui John Brincks. Venez attendre ici. Come in
No, not down, up.
Non, pas en bas, en haut.
Upstair
Upstair
- There you go - OK
- Là, vous montez - OK
My friends, this is Miss Turner from New York.
Mes amis, voici Miss Turner de New-York.
- We see her panties there. - Nice equipment
- On voit sa culotte là. - Beau matériel
Don't worry, she'll rule.
T'inquiète pas elle va assurer.
Oh yeah
Oh yeah
She sucks with american style. I feel her tonsils on my dick.
Elle suce à l'américaine. Je sens ses amygdales au bout de mon gland.
- I put you on all fours - "levrette", yeah (means: doggy)
- Je t'enfile en levrette - "levrette", yeah (means: doggy style)
You can't sing with your mouth full
Tu ne peux pas chanter la bouche pleine
Well it works for you! You changed your instrument.
Eh bien ça marche pour vous! Tu as changé d'instrument.
Wait, I have a good contract for you. We'll get the money!
Attends, j'ai un bon contrat pour toi. A nous le fric!
Here, sign here.
Tiens, signe ici.
I sign
I sign
-  Any dow payment ? - Yes, don't worry, there's your checks with
- Any dow payment? - Oui oui, ne t'inquiète pas, il y a vos chèques avec
Wow, where is my check?
Super, where is my check?
Here's the check
Et voilà le chèque
"Merci beaucoup!"
Merci beaucoup!
"???? ..."
"????..."
"... Avenue Foch. See you. John."
"...Avenue Foch, See you. John."
Avenue Foch now at this hour, it won't be easy
Avenue Foch à cette heure-ci, ça ne vapas être facile
Hurry up. "Moi" appointment. "Baiser".
Hurry up. "Moi" appointment. "Baiser".
- It is I who am fucked when you suck. -  "Baiser", "foutre", fuck ...
- C'est moi qui suis baisé quand tu suces. - "Baiser", "foutre", fuck, ...
Paris by night is nice. Oh! Moulin Rouge!
Paris by night is nice. Oh! Moulin Rouge!
She never saw anything. Not a suprise, her nose is always in the zips
Elle n'a jamais rien vu. Pas étonnant si elle circule toujours le nez dans les braguettes
- Well, here is your Moulin. - French Cancan
- Tiens, le voilà ton Moulin. - French Cancan
- Oh, Opera of Paris - Of course. Not of Vaicons-les-Bruyeres
- Oh, Opera de Paris - Oui, pas de Vaicons-les-Bruyères
- "Baiser, Opera"? - Perhaps, behind the scenes
- Baiser, Opera? - Peut-être, dans les coulisses
If she stops there it will turn on all the chorus
(Si elle s'arrête là elle va faire un malheur chez les choristes)
- Oh, Conciergerie! - It's not possible, she learned by heart the guide?
Oh, Conciergerie! (C'est pas possible, elle a appris le guide par coeur?)
- Oh, Notre-Dame! - Stop! No profanity!
- Oh, Notre-Dame! - Stop! Pas de blasphème!
-  Eiffel Tower ! - No, this is the "Tour Eiffel"!
- Eiffel Tower! - C'est la Tour Eiffel ça!
(Strange that she's wrong about the most famous monument in Paris)
(C'est marrant qu'elle se trompe sur le monument le plus célèbre de Paris)
-  Climb the Eiffel Tower ? - I'll climb you...
- Grimper dans Tour Eiffel? - Je vais te grimper moi...
- Say, we go to avenue Foch? -  Les Champs !
- Dis, on va bien avenue Foch? - Les Champs!
Champs on a Friday night it won't be easy.
Les Champs un vendredi soir ça ne va pas être facile.
Luckily, bikers are not there yet
On a de la chance que les motards ne soient pas encore là
What the Fuck Those guys are doing there?
What the fuck those guys are doing there?
Shit, the voyeurs of Fridays. I wouldn't have had to go through it.
Merde, les voyeurs du vendredi. Je n'aurais pas dû passer par là.
-  What ? - Voyeurs.
- What? - Voyeurs.
-  Oh, voyeurs. Stop - Do not worry, they'll do it.
- Ah, voyeurs. Stop - Ne t'inquiète pas, ils vont s'en charger.
Clear, there is nothing to see!
Dégagez, il n'y a rien à voir!
Crazy guys, I told you there's nothing to see
Bande de malades, je vous dit qu'il n'y a rien à voir
I'm going to lose my health. But it's not often we can drive an American girl
Je vais m'user la santé moi. Mais ce n'est pas tous les jours qu'on promène une américaine.
Nice
Nice
What is she doing? Show your tits!
Qu'est-ce qu'elle fout? Montre tes seins!
Show your pussy, so we can eat it!
Montre ta chatte qu'on te la bouffe!
Damn, this cunt!
Putain, ce trou!
Come on gentlemen, "branlez bien"
Come on gentlemen, "branlez" bien
She knows the French vocabulary!
Elle connaît bien le vocabulaire français!
"Jouir, bien branler, bon branlette"
"Jouir, bien branler, bon branlette"
Not as good as between your thighs
Pas aussi bon qu'entre tes cuisses
- You're enjoying, right? Bastards! - Bastard yourself!
- Il y en a qui se régalent, hein? Salauds de voyeurs! - Voyeur toi-même!
I'm cuming
Je vais éjaculer
"Ejaculater" come! I like "ejaculer"
"Ejaculer", come! I like "éjaculer"
My car! Hey, stop that guys.
Ma bagnole! Hey, arrêtez le massacre les gars.
"Bon grosse bite, Jeannot" (means: pretty big dick)
Bon grosse bite, Jeannot"
"Grosse bite" lying. Completed.
"Grosse bite" couchée. Terminé.
Straight to the Foch avenue, not far
En avant pour l'avenue Foch, ce n'est pas loin
Oh yes, Avenue Foch, if you clean your window maybe you can find it
Oh yes, Avenue Foch, if you clean your window maybe you can find it
Oh yes more, keep going, more
Oh yes more, keep going, more
It turns to delirium. What a talkative chick.
Ca tourne au délire. Quelle bavarde cette gonzesse.
Great, fantastic!
Great, fantastic!
"Fantastic" but I still see nothing.
"Fantastique" mais moi je ne vois toujours rien.
It's extra
It's extra
She thinks only about sex. Shit, the cops.
Elle pense qu'au sexe. Merde, les flics.
- Line up. - Why?
- Rangez vous. - Ah bon pourquoi?
- Your papers!
- Vos papiers!
So, can I see those papers?
Ca vient ces papiers?
-  Here ! - Here.
- Here! - Voilà.
- You often drive with a fog on your windshield?
- Ca vous arrive souvent de circuler avec un brouillard sur votre pare-brise?
- Well ... That is to say ...
- Bah... C'est-à-dire...
- You can not clean it?
- Vous ne pouvez pas le nettoyer?
- My nozzle no longer works. - Let me look
- Mon gicleur ne marche plus. - Faîtes voir
-  Here comes the "gicleur"  (means: nozzle)
- Here comes the "gicleur"
- "It does not work anymore", eh?
- "Il ne marche plus", hein?
It will cost you 500 Francs. Payable immediately.
Ca vous coûtera 500 Francs. Payable tout de suite.
And feel happy that I don't take you to the police station for contempt agent.
Et estimez vous heureux que je ne vous amène pas au poste de police pour outrage à agent.
And clean! It makes a bad impression for tourists.
Et nettoyez! Ca fait mauvaise impression pour les touristes.
Come on, I do not want to delay your lovely customer.
Allez, je ne veux pas retarder votre jolie cliente.
Thank you "Mr. Agent"
Thank you "Monsieur l'agent"
Junk! Bastard! Fuck you!
Ordure! Fumier! Salaud! Va te faire enculer!
Quick Mr! "Partouze" Avenue Foch  (means: bang)
Quick "Monsieur"! "Partouze", Avenue Foch
- Get out asshole! - Jeannot? - What is it again?
- Va-t-en connard! - Jeannot? - Qu'est-ce qu'il y a encore?
-  "partouze", "vite", Avenue Foch
- "Partouze", "vite", Avenue Foch
"Bang", "Fuck", what a vocabulary. But she doesn't understand other words
"Partouze", "Baiser", joli vocabulaire. Mais à part ça elle ne comprend rien
Well that's enough!
Eh bien "ras la quéquette"!
Besides there is on the Avenue Foch. No need to ask me the bill, it's free tonight.
D'ailleurs on y est sur l'Avenue Foch. Pas la peine de me demander l'addition, c'est gratuit ce soir.
Compris? Capito? Understand?
Compris? Capito? Voilà, compris?
It's enough for me.
J'en ai marre moi.
Here we are. "Merci Mr". Take care.
Here we are. "Merci monsieur". Take care.
My wife will be angry: my pants are dirty, I lost 700 Francs. Thank you Americans ...
Ca va être ma fête à la maison: j'ai salis mon pantalon, j'ai perdu 700 Francs. Merci les américains...
But I do have a good laugh when the cop took the sperm in the face.
J'ai quand même bien rigolé quand le flic a pris le sperme en plein visage.
I have lost money, but it was worth it.
J'ai perdu de l'argent, mais ça valait le coup.
It was too late. John Prick, my friend, he's gone. We can meet _him_ there
It was too late. John Prick, my friend, he's gone. We can meet him there
-  What's the matter ? - Completed. I'm fed up.
- What's the matter? - Terminé. J'en ai marre.
-  Let's go - Good-bye
- Let's go - Good bye
Well ... ok ... bye
Well... ok... bye
Totally crazy. She's going to pass a bad time. Whores do not like to trampling their turf.
Complètement dingue. Elle va passer à la casserole. Les putes n'aiment pas qu'on piétine leurs plates-bandes.
Go away. This is our yard here.
Pars! Barre-toi. C'est chez nous ici.
Your turn Jeannot!
A toi de jouer Jeannot!
Oh the girls, what happens?
Oh les gamines, qu'est-ce qui se passe?
Who's that one?
Qui c'est celui-là?
Oh, didn't you say it was for a foursome
Ah, fallait le dire que c'était pour une partie carrée (means: foursome)
-  "Partie carree? yes!" - Hey girlfriends you do not get it? I'm just the taxi driver
- "Partie carrée? yes!" - Hey les copines vous ne pigez pas? Je ne suis que le chauffeur de taxi
- We have no bias! - You don't but my wife does!
- On n'a pas de préjugés! - Toi peut-être mais ma femme elle en a!
Change your mind, yeah. "Sucer la chatte"
Change your mind, yeah. "Sucer le chatte"
Pretty one...
Jolie...
Hey, Jeannot, bitch "sucer bien bite"?
Hey, Jeannot, bitch "sucer bien bite"?
- Not bad Thank you. And you, "bitch sucking pussy well"? -  Fantastic
- Pas mal, merci. Et toi, "bitch sucer bien chatte" ? - Fantastic
- Come in my ass - With pleasure
- Viens dans mon cul - Avec plaisir
"Bien le cul Jeannot"? You like my "doigt"?
"Bien le cul Jeannot"? You like my "doigt"?
She pushes it deep, bitch!
Elle me l'enfonce profond la garce!
Oh my balls, they will explode
Ah mes valseuses, elles vont craquer.
Oh look what I've found here! Very "interessant"
Oh look what I've found here! Very "interessant"
you like suprise party Jeannot?
you like suprise party Jeannot?
Surprise? With you nothing surprises me.
Surprise? Avec toi rien ne me surprend.
Not this time ... This time gonna be a real surprise!
Not this time... This time gonna be a real surprise!
Your tongue in my ass ...  please
Ta langue dans mon cul... please
Oh I love Paris
Oh I love Paris
Let your neighbor's clit alone and take care of my ass
Laisse le cilto de ta voisine en face et occupe-toi de mon cul
Shit! A dick! A shemale!
Merde! Une bite! Un travesti!
Come to mine, my "minette" is "prete"
Come to mine, my "minette" is "prête"
I like it. "La queue j'aime"
I like it. "La queue j'aime"
A real nymphomaniac.
Une vraie nymphomane.
What do you prefer Jeannot? My "pussy" or "the ass" of the whore?
What do you prefer Jeannot? My "chatte" or "le cul" of the "pute"?
Oh I am a little sexist. I like your pussy.
Ah je suis un peu sexiste. J'aime bien ta chatte.
Go on horseback!
Allez, à cheval!
Swallow my dick with your pussy, my sweet slut
Avale ma queue avec ta chatte ma petite salope
I love french "queue"
I adore french "queue"
- This one is Brazilian ... -  Nevermind
- Celle-là est brésilienne... - Nevermind
- I come. -  Give it to me
- Je jouis, je viens. - Give it to me
- Liz, come with me I'm coming. -  Ejaculate
- A moi Liz, viens avec moi j'arrive. - Ejaculate
-  Hmmm Chantilly cream
- Hmmm Chantilly cream
I'll give you the whipped cream ...
Je t'en donnerai de la crème Chantilly...
Hey man, it's not free!
Dis donc mec, ce n'est pas gratuit tout ça...
In the pocket of my pants
Dans la poche de mon pantalon
- Should not be angry Jeannot - I'm not a billionaire
- Faut pas fâcher Jeannot - Je ne suis pas milliardaire moi
-  Bravo, Good job Jeannot
- Bravo, Good job Jeannot
-  Good job, really
- Good job, really
- OK it's fine.
- ok, ça va.
Hey, talking about job where you go now?
Dis donc, en parlant de job, où on va maintenant?
We will join a club for exchanges of all kinds.
On va rejoindre un club pour des échanges en tout genre.
- A Nogent. - At that point ...
- A Nogent. - Au point où j'en suis...
I'm not in a hurry to go home
Je ne suis pas pressé de rentrer à la maison
Let's go
Allez on y va
Hello, hi
Hello, hi
I'm looking for John Prick, he's a friend of mine
I'm looking for John Prick, he's a friend of mine
A good fucker, a real sex machine
A good fucker, a real sex machine
- What she's talking about? - She's looking for her friend, an American
- De quoi elle cause là? - Elle cherche un pote, un américain
Blond, with a large cock if I understood
Blond, avec une grande queue si j'ai bien compris
His name's Prick
Il s'appelle Prick
You don't know him?
Vous ne voyez pas?
I do, you should have said it before!
Si, il fallait le dire!
It is not there, but he will be back soon
Il n'est pas là, mas il ne va pas tarder
- But I don't wanna wait, I'm working! - Me too
- Mais je n'ai pas que ça à faire, je travaille! - Moi aussi
Look Jeannot
Look Jeannot
Jeannot, look!
Jeannot, look!
"Beaucoup queues"  (means: lot of cocks)
"Beaucoup queues" (means: lot of cocks)
- Come Jeannot ! - You want a "gum"? If there it makes you please...
- Come Jeannot! - Tu veux une "gum"? S'il n'y a que ca pour te faire plaisir...
No
No!
"Tout ces couilles, sucer couilles"  (means: suck the balls)
"Tout ces couilles, sucer les boules" (means: suck the balls)
"Sucking balls"? This is not the same price!
"Sucer couilles"? C'est pas le même prix!
- It is 1000 francs for the girl - Hey, I'm married!
- C'est 1000 francs pour la fille - Hey, je suis marié moi!
Me too. Exactly, that's how we can exchange
Moi aussi. Justement, c'est comme ça qu'on peut échanger
Besides your wife has already understood that
D'ailleurs ta femme a déjà compris
My wife? ... Well, go.
Ma femme? ... bon, allez.
So there it is. There will be a bad party for me when I'll be home....
Tiens, voilà. ça va être ma fête en rentrant à la maison
This is already your party!
C'est déjà ta fête!
I know you: "singer". You don't mind?
I know you: "chanteuse". You don't mind?
- A little suck? - Okay with pleasure
- Une petite sucette? - Oh ce n'est pas de refus
it feels good
ça fait du bien
Suck in chorus ladies! Nothing like that to be in a good shape
Sucez en choeur mesdames! Rien de tel qu'une bonne partie de lèche-gland pour mettre en forme
- Do you like "suck balls" Jeannot ? - You're so healthy!
- You like "sucer couilles", Jeannot? - Toi tu as de la santé!
-  Come here - Take it, it's yours
- Come here - Prends-la elle est à toi
-  I "suck" your "cock" - And I "lick" your "pussy"
- I "suce" your "bite" - And I "lèche" your "chatte"
-  Good you "lick" my "pussy" Jeannot - Take care of my dick. I want it very hard to put it in your ass
- Good you "lèche" my "chatte", Jeannot - Occupe toi de ma bite. Je veux qu'elle soit bien dure pour te la mettre dans le cul
- You can do two things at once? - Which means... - Use your fingers
- Tu peux faire deux choses à la fois? - C'est-à-dire que... - Utilise tes doigts
You got one in pussy. You gonna tell me what you think with one in the mouth
T'en as une dans la chatte. Tu vas me dire ce que tu en penses dans la bouche
Bastard, you spit me in the face! Look!
Salaud, tu m'as craché en pleine gueule! Tiens!
The pleasure is mine...
Tout le plaisir est pour moi...
- This is a swingers club here ... - It can still be used
- C'est un club échangiste ici... - Elle peut encore servir
There is a cat meowing there
Il y a une chatte qui miaule là-bas
-  Oh my goodness (??)
- Oh my goodness (??)
- She says anything to get interesting
- Elle dit n'importe quoi pour se rendre intéressante
"Tu es doux, ton queue est pas bandé enough" (means: you're not hard enough")
"Tu es doux, ton queue est pas bandé enough" (means: you're not hard enough")
Hey, "Vive la France!". We do it well here too. Come inside.
Hey, "vive la france!". On fait bien ici aussi. Vient à l'intérieur.
- Can be OK - You're so rude!
- ça peut aller - t'es gonflé!
Hello!
Coucou!
How are you Johnny?
How are you Jeannot?
It's okay
ça va
Oh, interesting, what is it?
Oh, interesting, what is it?
You don't know it in America? yet you have invented the sandwich
Vous ne connaissez pas en amérique, vous avez pourtant inventé le sandwich
I love, I wanna try
I love, I want to try
It's "big". It's a "big cock". "Hello".
It's "grosse". It's a "grosse bite". "Bonjour".
-  Oh, Jeannot, I want my "queue" ... - OK
- Oh, Jeannot, je veux ma queue... - ok
it will change you
ça va te changer
Hey you, your "queue" in my mouth
Hey you, your "queue" in my mouth
She speaks with her hands. Tony, the rescue!
Elle parle avec les mains. Tony, du secours!
What should we do?
Qu'est-ce qu'on fait?
Ah, the american girls, they want it all!
Ah, les américains ils veulent tout avoir!
Hey, gently, girls!
Hey, doucement les filles!
Come come
Viens, viens
Come, nevermind
Viens laisse tomber
John Prick is a myth
Le dénommé Prick est un mythe
If we keep on looking for him, I'll lose my health and my shirt
Si on doit le chercher encore longtemps je vais y laisser ma santé et ma chemise
Oh! John! You son of a bitch!
Oh! John! Yous on of a bitch!
Where have you been all fucking night?
Where Have you been all fucking night?
It's nice John, come!
It's nice John, come!
- Yoohoo - Oh, you're here
- Yoohoo - Ah you're here!
all night Fucking, fucking French, fantastic!
Fucking all night, French fucking, fantastic!
Come on Baby!
Come on Baby!
Fuck! A dwarf!
Putain, un nain!
Baby it's been too long. Let's take it off
Baby it's been too long. Let's take it off
Show me your pussy
Show me your pussy
you make it good
you make it good
Oh my lover
Oh my lover
Fucking American fucking
Je t'en foutrais de la baise américaine moi
Slut, whore, bitch
Salope, trainée
Oh and shit
Ah et puis merde
Hey, my car!
Hey, ma voiture!
Oh shit...
Oh merde...
I swear you-have the best pussy
I swear you have the best pussy
Jeannot is it okay?
ça va Jeannot?
- You? - My car! You wrecked my car!
- Vous? - Ma voiture! Vous êtes rentré dans ma voiture!
Who's going to pay me this?
Qui est-ce qui va me payer ca?
It's not so serious...
C'est pas grave...
(they continue to argue)
(ils continuent à se disputer)
You're so fucking wet
You're so fucking wet
I'll write you a check
Je vais vous faire un chèque
What are you waiting for? My check!
Qu'est-ce que vous attendez, vous me le faîtes ce chèque?
- So it's coming this check? - Yes, yes, we have time, one minute ...
- Alors ça vient ce chèque? - Oui oui, on a le temps, minute...
I'm coming
I'm coming
Here's your check
Voilà votre chèque